http://tisingervance.com/privacy-policy

Tisinger Vance, P.C. Privacy Policy
We recognize and respect the privacy expectations of today’s consumers and the requirements of the applicable federal and state privacy laws.  We understand that you may be concerned about what we will do with certain information, particularly any personal or financial information.  We agree that you have a right to know how we will utilize this personal information that you will provide to us.  Therefore, we have adopted this Private Policy to govern the use and handling of your personal information.
We collect non-public, personal information about you from the following sources:
Information that we receive from you, such as your name, address, telephone number,  and social security number.
Information about your transaction with us, our clients, our affiliates or others.  We receive this information from your lender, attorney, real estate broker, etc.
Information from public records.
We request information about you for our own legitimate business purposes and not for the benefit of any non-affiliated party; therefore, we will not release your information to any non-affiliated party except (1)as is necessary for us to use a  product or service that you have requested of us;  (2) or as permitted by law.  We may, however, store such information indefinitely including the period after which any customer relationship has ceased.
We strive to assure no unauthorized parties have access to your information.  We currently maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with Federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.
770-834-4467
